tvtropes.org 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - TV Tropes

Thank you for visiting TVTropes. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this wiki. Please read this privacy policy before using the wiki or submitting any personal information. By using the wiki, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the wiki to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

Note : the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this [wiki](https://tvtropes.org/) only. If you link to other wikis, please review the privacy policies posted at those wikis. 

### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The wiki uses cookie and tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the wiki, and understanding how visitors use the wiki. Cookies can also help customize the wiki for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

  * Partner Cookie Policies

### What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to the wiki.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on visits to the wiki and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. 

### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this wiki allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:   
By e-mail: dr at tvtropes.org   
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
